(Raj:)Oh, but there's money
for a drawer full of Red Vines,
(Raj:)a marshmallow shooting rifle,
(Raj:)and a super executive ant farm
with glow-in-the-dark sand?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Howard:)Okay, what if he
buys his own desk?
(Raj:)Yeah, what
if I buy my own desk?
(Sheldon:)That's ridiculous.
Why?
(Katee Sackhoff:)Because...
(Raj:)Yes?
(Sheldon:)It's my office.
(Howard(laughs):)Sheldon.
All right, all right.
(Sheldon:)He can buy his own desk.
(Raj:)And I can put it in your office?
(Sheldon:)Well, you really want
(Sheldon:)to dot the I's and cross
the T's, don't you?
(Leonard:)Why would you want
a glow-in-the-dark ant farm?
(Sheldon:)They do some
of their best work at night.
(Penny(picking up a top and sniffing it):)Ah, it's okay.
(Sheldon:)Penny?